#大家好 我們這個新廠房差不多搞好啦
Hi everyone! Our new site is now almost ready.
#我們看一下上次那個黃蜂窩哇 有沒有跑掉
We'll have a look at the wasp nest that we discovered last time. Let's see if it's still here.
#要把它搞掉 不搞掉的話 等一下去蟄到我們的
We need to remove it. We might get stung if we don't.
#到時候我們要搬到這裡來住
Cuz we'll be moving in later.
#哇 你看 買了那麼多水泥
Wa! Look! We've bought a lot of cement.
#備用的
They're in reserve.
#哎喲 這裡有一個掃把
Ayo! Here's a broom.
#拿這個掃把來防蟄
Alright! It will be my cover.
#等下蟄我不好辦啊
I would be too bad if I got stung.
#就在這裡面
It's here inside.
#你看 這個 黃蜂窩 現在好大了啊
Look! The, the wasp nest, is now that large.
#還挨著這個門上
It's even lying on the door,
#就在門的旁邊
right next to the door.
#我進這裡面都進不去
I can't even get into the room.
#我要把它搞掉
I'll get rid of it.
#你看 在就 在就這門口擋著啦
Look! It's, it's here, blocking the doorway.
#讓我進都進不去
I can't even get it.
#你們該搬家啦 這樣不行的
You guys need to move out. It will be a problem.
#就一個
Just one
#哈哈哈
Ha ha ha
#你看 這個黃蜂 黃蜂啊 全部都飛走啦
Look! The wasp, and the larvae, have all flown away.
#現在一個子都沒有啦 空的
Now it's empty, nothing left.
#可能它們準備過冬啦
They must be preparing for the winter.
#它們從新搬了一個家
So they have moved to a new home.
#一個都沒有
Not even one.
#想吃一個都沒有
Not even one for me to eat.
#哇 有一個很小的
Wa! There's a really small one.
#那麼小
It's so small,
#用牙簽才撩得到它
that I almost need a toothpick to pick it out.
#哦 一點點 像個小蟲子一樣
Oh! Just a tiny little bit, like a small worm.
#就一個
Just one.
#你看 搞了一個黃蜂子都沒有的
Look! I ah, well, there's not even one larvae.
#白搞啦
It wastes my time.
#冒著生命危險 搞了一個空包
I risked my life, only to have an empty nest.
#好啦 今天的視頻就到這裡啦
Alright! The video ends here.